Contact

khushbujain091@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/khushbujain-240349171 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Recruiting
Job Analysis
HR Management

Khushbu Jain

Hiring great talent for our fast growing tech platform (HR) - on a mission to make employment easier & rewarding # Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India

Summary

I was always told that I am a good listener, well how else to use this quality effectively other than being an HR. Listening is required first to understand and then solve Employees Problem. Those inbuilt skills of mine I then validated with getting Degree with Specialization in Business and Management. I later on figured out that its not only Employees issues that needs to be addressed but I needed to be a bridge between Company Management and Employee and that's where my Journey started of building a bridge....

Experience

TechnoSouls
Human Resources Executive
June 2021 - Present (1 year 10 months)
Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India

HR responsibilities.

Employees' Joining to exit formalities.

Employee Induction program.

Resolving employees' queries & issues.

Attendance management.

Events organisation, celebration planning & co-ordination.

Time to time employees feedback kind of survey & taking session for skill improvement of employees.

Zealous System

Human Resources Executive September 2020 - May 2021 (9 months)

Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India

My Focus is mainly on maintaining an Environment where Ideas can be shared and Creativity is Appreciated.

Digging deep into my Daily Activities I am accountable for

Company Policy Making and Implementation.

Employee Relations, Business Partnering,

Discuss Employees' Career Development and Succession Planning

Monitor HR metrics (e.g. turnover rates and cost-per-hire)

Payroll and Taxation,

Performance Evaluation Appraisal

Well it doesnt end here as Employee Issues dont end here but list will go on if I write everything here...

AddWeb Solution Private Limited
Human Resources Associate
September 2018 - September 2020 (2 years 1 month)
Ahmedabad Area, India

Responsible for end to end recruitment for IT Positions starting from Junior to senior level.

Sourcing of the relevant profiles from the various job portals such as Naukri, shine and LinkedIn etc.

Taking preliminary interview, Handled salary negotiations & salary dispensation approvals maintaining equilibrium between organizations offering and candidate's expectations. providing full work support to HR Manager and involved in day-to-day operations.

Identifying the candidates on different parameters like communication skills, technical skills, previous experience etc.

Plan employee engagement activities & Award events.

Creating & maintaining Database for resourcing.

HR Policy adherence and processing in the organization.

Taking telephonic round and first round of Interview of the Candidates.

Education

Maharaja collage Udaipur

Master of Business Administration - MBA, HR

Vikram University, Ujjain

B.com, Business Administration and Management, General